A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, RG 3 FA1401
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, 3
  - General Files, 1
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, 1984 March 5-6 (Box 304, Folder 12)
    - American Members Meeting, 1984 December 14 (Box 304, Folder 13)
    - Media Committee, Meeting of American Members, 1985 December 3 (Box 304, Folder 14)
    - Museum Committee, Meeting of American Members, 1985 November 6 (Box 304, Folder 15)
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, 1985 June 20-21 (Box 304, Folder 16)
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, 1985 June 20-21 (Box 304, Folder 17)
    - Joint Film and Broadcasting Meeting in India, 1985 March 4-5 (Box 304, Folder 18)
    - Joint Museum Committee Meeting in India, 1985 February 28-March 1 (Box 304, Folder 19)
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, 1986 March 25-26 (Box 304, Folder 20)
    - Joint Commission Meeting, 1986 February 6 (Box 304, Folder 21)
    - Meeting of Joint Media Committee, 1986 February 13-14 (Box 304, Folder 22)
    - Joint Museum Committee Meeting, 1986 February 10-11 (Box 304, Folder 23)
    - American Members Meeting, Joint Indo-US Subcommission, 1986 January 7 (Box 304, Folder 24)
    - American Members, Media Committee, 1986 October 15 (Box 304, Folder 25)
    - American Members, Museum Committee, 1986 October 9 (Box 304, Folder 26)
    - American Members, Joint Committee on Cultural Heritage and Endeavor, 1987 December 10 (Box 304, Folder 27)
    - American Members Media Committee, NYC, 1987 October 13 (Box 304, Folder 28)
    - Joint Sub-commission, 1987 March 16-17 (Box 304, Folder 29)
    - American Members Meeting, Joint Sub-commission, 1987 February 20 (Box 304, Folder 30)
    - Briefing Materials, Joint Sub-commission Meeting, Austin, Texas, 1987 (Box 304, Folder 31)
    - Bangalore, Joint Meeting of Media Committee, 1987 January 8-9 (Box 304, Folder 32)
    - Joint Meeting of Museum Committee, Bangalore, 1987 January 5-6 (Box 304, Folder 33)
    - American Members Sub-commission, 1988 December 6 (Box 304, Folder 34)
    - Joint Committee on Cultural Heritage and Endeavor, American Members Meeting, 1988 November 1 (Box 304, Folder 35)
    - Joint Media Committee, American Members? Meeting, 1988 October 24 (Box 304, Folder 36)
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, New Delhi, 1988 March 1-2 (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Meeting of the Joint Committee on Cultural Heritage and Endeavor, Los Angeles, 1988 February 4-5 (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - Joint Media Committee Meeting, Los Angeles, 1988 Febraury 1-2 (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - American Members Meeting, Joint Sub-Commission, NY, 1988 January 15 (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - American Members? Joint Committee on Culture, Washington, D. C., 1989 November 27 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - American Members? Meeting, Joint Media Committee, NY, 1989 November 14 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, Washington, D. C., 1989 June 29-30 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - Joint Media Committee Meeting, India, 1990 December 3-4 (Box 305, Folder 8)
    - Joint Committee Meetings in India, 1989 February (Box 305, Folder 9)
    - Joint Committee on Culture, New Delhi, 1990 November 29-30 (Box 305, Folder 10)
    - American Members Meeting of Culture-Media Committee, 1990 September 24 (Box 305, Folder 11)
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, New Delhi, 1990 March 29-30 (Box 305, Folder 12)
    - Joint Media Committee Meeting, Washington, D. C., 1990 January 23 (Box 305, Folder 13)
    - Joint Cultural Committee Meeting, Washington, D. C., 1990 January 22 (Box 305, Folder 14)
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, Brown University, 1991 April 9-10 (Box 305, Folder 15)
    - Joint Culture Committee Meeting, NYC, 1991 November 18-19 (Box 305, Folder 16)
    - Joint Media Committee Meeting, NYC, 1991 November 21-22 (Box 305, Folder 17)
    - American Members Meeting, Sub-Commission, 1991 December 9 (Box 305, Folder 18)
    - Sub-commission, American Members Meeting, NY, 1992 December 7 (Box 305, Folder 19)
    - Information 2000 Plus Joint Meeting, 1992 November 3-5 (Box 305, Folder 20)
    - Info 2000 Plus Meeting, 1992 July 9 (Box 305, Folder 21)
    - Information 2000 Plus Program Meeting, 1992 May 4-5 (Box 305, Folder 22)
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, New Delhi, 1992 February 3-5 (Box 305, Folder 23)
    - Sub-commission, American Members Meetings, NYC, 1993 December 1 (Box 305, Folder 24)
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, Washington, D. C., 1993 April 19-20 (Box 305, Folder 25)
    - Information 2000 Plus, American Members Meeting, NYC, 1993 November 12 (Box 305, Folder 26)
    - Program Meeting, 1994 November 2 (Box 305, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, Prime Minister?s Visit, Sackler Gallery, 1994 May 18 (Box 305, Folder 28)
    - Joint Sub-commission Meeting, 1995 Spring (Box 305, Folder 29)
    - Joint Meeting, New Delhi, 1994 February 15-16 (Box 305, Folder 30)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1995 December (Box 305, Folder 31)
    - American Members Meeting, NYC, 1995 December 12 (Box 305, Folder 32)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meeting, NYC, 1995 April 19-20 (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - Joint Meeting, New Delhi, 1996 March 7-8 (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - Indian Members of IUSSCEC, Copies (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - American Members of the IUSSCEC, Copies (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - Joint Committee on Culture, American Members (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - Joint Media Committee, American Members (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - Info 2000 Plus Advisory Committee (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Culture, Indian Members (Box 306, Folder 8)
    - Media Committee, Indian Members (Box 306, Folder 9)
    - Travel Agreement with ICCR (Box 306, Folder 10)
    - Sub-commission Members, American Secretariat, Current (Box 306, Folder 11)
    - Sub-commission, Info on American Members, Rotation, etc (Box 306, Folder 12)
    - Indo-US Subcommission Brochures (Box 306, Folder 13)
    - Original Programs, Cumulative 17 years (Box 306, Folder 14)
    - Sub-commission, Memos (Box 306, Folder 15)
    - Sub-commission, General Correspondence (Box 306, Folder 16)
    - Pritzker, Thomas J. (Box 306, Folder 17)
    - Tanen, Ted M. G. (Box 306, Folder 18)
    - Blitzer, Charles, Sub-commission Member, Old Correspondence (Box 306, Folder 19)
    - Blitzer, Charles (Box 306, Folder 20)
    - ICCR, Indian Council for Cultural Relations (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - Pradeep Mehendiratta, AIIS, General Correspondence (Box 307, Folder 2)
  - Grant Files, 2
    - IAFP Funding, Smithsonian Grant, 006738, 1980-1981 (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, SI Grant 80566300, DS-8804, 1988 June 1; 1990 December 31 (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - Sub-commission IAFP, DS-8703, Smithsonian 70470800, 1987 June 1-1989 October 31 (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - IAFP 1989-1990, Smithsonian Grant 90612900, DS-8903, 1989 July 1-1990 November 30 (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, Reduction of Program, General Correspondence (Box 307, Folder 7)
    - Smithsonian Instittue (SI) Grant FR00596100 for IAFP, 1990 July 1-1992 March 31 (Box 307, Folder 8)
    - SI-IAFP FR20671200, Financial Memos-Adjustments (Box 307, Folder 9)
    - SI-IAFP FR20671200, Financial Reports (Box 307, Folder 10)
    - SI-IAFP FR20671200, Grant Letter (Box 307, Folder 11)
    - SI-IAFP FR10548900, Financial Memos-Adjustments (Box 307, Folder 12)
    - SI-IAFP FR10548900, Grant Letter-Amendments (Box 307, Folder 13)
    - NSF INT-8604523, DS-8604, 1986 June 15-1989 November 30 (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - NSF INT 8604523, Proposal, Contract, Final Narrative and Financial Reports, 1986 June 15-1989 November 30 (Box 308, Folder 2)
    - NSF Grant INT-8319268, Final Financial and Narrative Reports, 1988 (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - NSF INT-8319268, DS-8404, IAFP, 1984-1986 (Box 308, Folder 4)
    - NSF INT-8015988, IAFP Funding, 1980 June 15-1983 May 31 (Box 308, Folder 5)
    - SFCP Grant Proposal for Secretariat Support, 00247100, 1979-1980 (Box 308, Folder 6)
    - SI Grant 20854300 for Joint Programs, 1983 September 8-1984 April 30 (Box 308, Folder 7)
    - Proposal to Smithsonian for Festival of India Conference, 41009400 (Box 308, Folder 8)
    - Sub-commission Joint Programs, DS-8702, Smithsonian 70470700, 1987 July 1-1989 February 28 (Box 308, Folder 9)
    - Joint Programs, Smithsonian Grant 80566400, DS-8803, 1988 July 1-1990 March 31 (Box 308, Folder 10)
    - Joint Program, Smithsonian Grant 60835500, Final Financial and Narrative Reports (Box 308, Folder 11)
    - USIS Grant IA-428-1305-G, DS-8708, 1987 (Box 308, Folder 12)
    - USIF IA-428-1351-G, DS-8801, Final Reports Submitted, FY 1988 (Box 308, Folder 13)
    - USIF IA-428-1441-G, USIS Status of Funds Reports, FY 1989 (Box 308, Folder 14)
    - USIF IA-428-1507-G, USIS Status of Funds Reports, FY 1990 (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - USIF Negotiations, FY 1990 (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - USIF IA-428-1574, Grant Agreement, FY 1991 (Box 309, Folder 3)
    - Special Projects Fund, Dance Troupes, Amended to 1574 (Box 309, Folder 4)
    - USIF IA-428-1574, Status of Funds Reports, FY 1991 (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - USIA, IA-18713-19-G, FY 1980 (Box 309, Folder 6)
    - USIA, IA-19595-19-G, FY 1981 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - USIA, IA-20111-19-G, FY 1982 (Box 309, Folder 8)
    - USIA, IA-20437-19-G, FY 1983 (Box 309, Folder 9)
    - USIA, IA-20974-19-G, FY 1984 (Box 309, Folder 10)
    - USIA, IA-PMSA-G8193120, FY 1988 (Box 309, Folder 11)
    - USIA, IA-PMSA-G9193483, FY 1989 (Box 309, Folder 12)
    - USIA, IS-PMSA-G0190019, FY 1990 (Box 309, Folder 13)
    - USIA, IA-PMSA-G0190019, Financial, FY 1990 (Box 309, Folder 14)
    - USIA, IA-PMSA-G1190011, FY 1991 (Box 309, Folder 15)
  - Festival of India, 3
    - Education Programs, Horizon Magazine, 1985 (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - Education Programs, Festival of India, Educational Materials (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - Education Programs, Awareness Program (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - Education Programs, Traveling Exhibitions of Photography, A200 (Box 310, Folder 4)
    - Education Programs, English-Speaking Union (Box 310, Folder 5)
    - Education Programs, India Book, Singh, Vijay, Abstracts, E40 (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - Education Programs, Correspondence, Festival Program Coordinators (Box 310, Folder 7)
    - Festival, General Info. Festival of India (FOI), Festival of India, Proposal for Stamp (Box 310, Folder 8)
    - Festival, General Info. Festival of India (FOI), Sheraton Hotels (Box 310, Folder 9)
    - Festival, General Info. Festival of India (FOI), Taj Group Hotels and Trade Wings Ltd (Box 310, Folder 10)
    - Festival, General Info. Festival of India (FOI), Festival of India (FOI) Graphics (Box 310, Folder 11)
    - Festival, General Info. Festival of India (FOI), Modi and Beckler Design, Festival of India (FOI), Stationary (Box 310, Folder 12)
    - Festival, General Info. Festival of India (FOI), Volunteer (Box 310, Folder 13)
    - Liaison with The White House (Box 310, Folder 14)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Public Relations (Box 310, Folder 15-16)
    - Festival of India (FOI), PR Budgets, etc (Box 310, Folder 17)
    - Festival, General Info. Festival of India (FOI), Festival Employment (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - Education Programs, Gandhi, A US Committee for UNICEF Educational (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Hotels, Airlines, etc (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Mahatma Gandhi Statue (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Festival of India (FOI) Logo Sheets (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Public Relations, Inaugural Concert, Kennedy Center, 1986 June 13 (Box 311, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations, Festival of India (FOI) 1985-1986 (Box 311, Folder 7)
    - Public Relations, Festival of India (FOI), Press Kit Originals (Box 311, Folder 8)
    - NY Press Kit, India, Correspondence, 1985 Janaury (Box 311, Folder 9)
    - NY Press Kit, Lincoln Center, Alice Tully Hall, "Festival of Music and Dance" (Box 311, Folder 10)
    - General Info, Fine Arts Committee, Festival of India (FOI), 1984-1985 (Box 311, Folder 11)
    - General Info, Finance Committee, Festival of India (FOI), G70 (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - General Info, Performing Arts Committee, Festival of India (FOI), G90 (Box 312, Folder 2)
    - General Info, Pan Asian Repertory Theater (Box 312, Folder 3)
    - General Info, Festival of India (FOI), Alice Tully Hall, 1985 September 10 (Box 312, Folder 4)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Committees and Meetings, Festival of India (FOI), Performing Arts, Theater Proposals (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Committees and Meetings, Festival of India (FOI), General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 312, Folder 6-7)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Committees and Meetings, Festival of India (FOI), General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 312, Folder 8)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Committees and Meetings (Box 312, Folder 9)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Committees and Meetings, Festival of India (FOI), General Invitation Lists (Box 312, Folder 10)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Committees and Meetings, Festival of India (FOI) Dinner, 1984 April 6 (Box 312, Folder 11)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Committees and Meetings, Festival of India (FOI), Photos (Box 312, Folder 12)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Committees and Meetings, Old Festival of India (FOI) Lists, 1986 January (Box 312, Folder 13)
    - Festival of India (FOI), Committees and Meetings, Festival of India (FOI) Lists (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Museum Exchange, 4
    - Museum Exchange, Pollack, Wendy, 1987 February (Box 313, Folder 2)
    - Museum Exchange, Archaeologist ASI, 1987 April (Box 313, Folder 3)
    - Museum Exchange, Sutton, John, 1985 December (Box 313, Folder 4)
    - Museum Exchange, Ganguly, T. K., 1985 April-July (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Museum Exchange, Ranade, Dilip, 1984 October-1985 January (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - Museum Exchange, General, 1985 (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - Museum Exchange, Jacob, Elizabeth, 1984 October-December (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - Museum Exchange, White, Marcia, 1984 November-December (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - Museum Exchange, Goswamy, S., 1984 March-April (Box 313, Folder 10)
    - Museum Exchange, General, 1984 (Box 313, Folder 11)
    - Museum Exchange, Lawton, T., 1984 (Box 313, Folder 12)
    - Museum Exchange, Usha, K., NMNH, 1983 October-December (Box 313, Folder 13)
    - Museum Exchange, Beach, Milo, Williams College, 1982 (Box 313, Folder 14)
    - Museum Exchange, Bisht, A. S., 1983 (Box 313, Folder 15)
    - Museum Exchange, Sanfacon, Paul, 1983 (Box 313, Folder 16)
    - Museum Exchange, Farooqi, Anis, 1982 March (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Museum Exchange, Date, Dutta, 1982 (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - Museum Exchange, Saha, P. K., 1982 (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Museum Exchange, Gupta, Satyender Kumar, 1982 (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Museum Exchange, General, 1982 (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Museum Exchange, Falk, John, 1982 (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Museum Exchange, Johnson, Nathaniel, AMNH, 1981-1982 (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - Museum Exchange, Carella, Elizabeth, Grantee, 1981 (Box 314, Folder 8)
    - Museum Exchange, Gupta, Pratima, 1981 (Box 314, Folder 9)
    - Museum Exchange, Ram, Devi, 1981 (Box 314, Folder 10)
    - Museum Exchange, General, 1983 (Box 314, Folder 11)
    - Museum Exchange, Hower, Rolland, 1981 (Box 314, Folder 12)
    - Museum Exchange, Bagchi, S. K., 1981 (Box 314, Folder 13)
    - Museum Exchange, General, 1981 (Box 314, Folder 14)
    - Museum Exchange, Friedman, Alan, 1980 (Box 314, Folder 15)
    - Museum Exchange, Pessino, C., 1980-1981 (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Museum Exchange, Gittinger, M., 1980-1981 (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - Museum Exchange, Smart, Ellen, 1980 (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - Museum Exchange, General, 1980 (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Museum Exchange, Sharma, R. and Harinarayana, 1979-1980 (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Museum Exchange, Koshy, M. and Gogate, V., 1979-1980 (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - Museum Exchange, Rosenfield, John, 1979-1980 (Box 315, Folder 7)
    - Museum Exchange, Arth, Malcolm, 1979-1980 (Box 315, Folder 8)
    - Museum Exchange, Ramamoorthy, S., 1979-1980 (Box 315, Folder 9)
    - Museum Exchange, Inger, Robert I., 1979 May (Box 315, Folder 10)
    - Museum Exchange, General, 1978-1979 (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - Museum Exchange, Kazi, R. B., 1978 (Box 315, Folder 12)
    - Exchange of Museum Personnel, Rajamahanty, Apparao, 1978-1979 (Box 316, Folder 1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Personnel material
    - Exchange of Museum Personnel, Basu, Shri Sukantu, 1978-1979 (Box 316, Folder 2)
    - Exchange of Museum Personnel, Mackie, Louise, 1978-1979 (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - Exchange of Museum Personnel, Ganam, N. M., 1978-1979 (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - Exchange of Museum Personnel, Possehl, Gregory, 1978-1979 (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - Exchange of Museum Personnel, Shelley, Marjorie, 1978-1979 (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - Exchange of Museum Personnel, Cassidy, Martin, 1977-1978 (Box 316, Folder 7)
    - Exchange of Museum Personnel, Museum Committee, AAM, 1976-1977 (Box 316, Folder 8)
  - Indo-US Subcommission Video Recordings, 5
    Moving Images
    - Eubie - Tape 1 of 2, 1983; U-matic (Box 1, Tape AV 11637)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - Eubie - Tape 2 of 2, 1983; U-matic (Box 1, Tape AV 11638)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact an RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - Barry Manilow Special - Tape 1 of 2, circa1980s; U-matic (Box 1, Tape AV 11639)
    - Barry Manilow Special - Tape 2 of 2, circa1980s; U-matic (Box 1, Tape AV 11640)
    - I Feel A Song Coming On - Tape 1 of 2, circa1980s; U-matic (Box 1, Tape AV 11641)
    - I Feel A Song Coming On - Tape 2 of 2, circa1980s; U-matic (Box 1, Tape AV 11642)
    - DSN Story, circa1980s; 22 minutes; U-matic (Box 1, Tape AV 11643)
      Scope and Contents
      Videotape from Jet Propulsion Laboratory (NASA) - Audiovisual Services Office/ California Institute of Technology
    - DSN Story, circa1980s; 22 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11646)
    - Voyager Encounters Highlights Tape, circa1980s; 31 minutes; U-matic (Box 2, Tape AV 11644)
    - Voyager Encounters Highlights Tape, circa1980s; 31 minutes; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11645)
    - Neptune Encounter Highlights Tape, 1989 September 14; 29 minutes; U-matic (Box 2, Tape AV 11647)
    - Neptune Encounter Highlights Tape, 1989 September 14; 29 minutes; U-Matic (Box 2, Tape AV 11648)
    - Aadmi Aur Aurat (English title: Man and Woman), India - Window on World Television, 1984; 56 minutes; U-matic (Box 2, Tape AV 11649)
      Hindi language Telefilm directed by Tapan Sinha and starring Amol Palekar, Mahua Roy Chawdhary. The movie was telecast on Doordarshan, Government owned TV Channel of India.
      Plot: A man and a woman travel through a jungle. When the man learns about the woman's pregnancy, he decides to accompany her on her journey and helps her overcome all the hurdles.
    - Museum Without Walls, Undated; Color, 1 minute; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11650)
      Indo-U.S. Sub Committee Exhibit - Science